# Michael Tran

michaelt437@gmail.com 240.678.4519 3031 Drummond Dr Finksburg, MD

#### Summary

Front end engineer with experience developing applications in Vuejs, SCSS, and TypeScript. I strive to efficiently build clean and user friendly interfaces and solutions using best practices and patterns. Worked on many agile teams to deliver features and goals on time.

#### Skills

Vuejs, TypeScript, SCSS, React, TailwindCSS, HTML5, JavaScript, Node, Jira, Bitbucket, Git

### **Experience**

## DealerOn, Inc.

Front End Engineer - DERWOOD, MD

06/2017 - Present

- Developed greenfield projects and major updates using Vuejs, Vuetify, TypeScript, and SCSS for Enterprise Specials Manager, Beacon Reporting application, Dealer Organizer application, Leads UI. Projects involved data visualization, with ESM including CRUD elements
- · Developed on and maintain APEX for digital retailing experiences, using PrimeVue and TailwindCSS
- Convert Beacon Reporting to vue-cli template with TypeScript
- Discuss and enforce decisions on standardizing tooling and planning for long-term infrastructure and architecture plans, including using TS, SCSS, Eslint, Miragejs
- Collaborate and iterate with UX team to build the best experience
- Occasionally navigate around TeamCity and Octopus for application builds

## DealerOn, Inc.

Junior Web Designer - DERWOOD, MD

05/2016 - 06/2017

- Fulfill client requests of edits and updates to dealer websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript through in-house CMS
- Build out home pages based on mocks and wireframes from clients
- · Design banners graphics in Photoshop

## **Howard Hughes Medical Institute**

Front End Developer Intern

06/2015 - 08/2015

- Implemented a debounce feature throughout the Science 360 web application
- Developed a Protractor script for End-to-end testing of entire Science 360 site
- · Created spreadsheet export function with customized styling
- Customized Flotchart plotting for lab census information

## Education

# Digital Media and Web Technologies

University of Maryland Global Campus